Today I'm in the mood for hamburger
今日の気分はハンバーガー
A special original burger
スペシャル☆オリジナルバーガー
I'll pile on all my favorite toppings
好きな具を重ねよう
Can't hold back my excitement
ワクワクが止まらない
Yup, even if you can go out and buy them at a restaurant
お店に行けば買えても
Homemade burgers still taste the best, right?
やっぱ手作り最強でしょ
My patissier blood is stirring
パティシエの血が騒ぐ
Come to my small burger shop!
おいで! 小さなハンバーガーショップ
Love is our à la mode topping
LOVE LOVE トッピング アラモード
It melts sweetly, it’ll make you smile
甘くとろけて笑顔つくるよ
Add a little lemonade to finish it off
仕上げに ちょっと レモネード
I’m giving you these “sweet” sweets
君に贈るよ ステキなスイーツ
Next is Dorayaki!
次はどら焼き
Cherry blossom petals fluttering down
桜の花びら
Pale pink sweet bean paste
薄紅色のアンコ
The tiny princess at the end of the fork
フォークの先よりちっちゃいお姫様
Jumps with all her might marks her brand, and completes her baking
全力でジャンプ 焼き印押したらできあがり
Dorayaki princess
どら焼き乙女
Bashful with cerise sweet sauce
恥じらう桜ソース
Delicious, graceful, elegant, joyful
おいし しゃなり はんなり うれし
Long live Japan's traditional ladies
大和撫子万歳
Sweet smells hanging in the air
甘い香りで
wake me up rather softly and slowly
ゆるりと目が覚めた
A feast, a dream, reality, left here
ご馳走 夢か うつつ 残し
But the princess has disappeared
お姫様は消えた
Happy happy sweets
ハ・ピ・ハ・ピ スウィーツ
And favourite crêpes
大好きクレープ
The guy I'm looking for
あたしの求めるアイツは
is someone that stands out a little from everyone else around
そこら辺にあるのとちょっとチガウ
Tell me something, anything, really, I don't already know
なになになに教えてよ
All right, yeah; well, can't you try and guess?
そうねーウン じゃあ当ててみて?
Apples? No, no!
林檎? NONO!
Natto? No, no!
納豆? NONO!
Well… miso? Ah, pretty close! Huh?!
じゃー...お味噌? あっ近い! えっ?!
The thing we're aiming for is the world's tallest peak
目指すは世界の最高峰
Good! Yeah, well, let's make some!
そうねー! うんじゃあ作りましょう!
Little incapable me has a wonderful recipe
未熟なアタシと不思議なレシピで
Hee haa hee haa~  Would you like to make it?
ひ~(は~)ひ~(は~) しませんか?
Let's have some spicy, spicy, spicy, spicy curry
からいからいからいからいカレーをメシアガレ(で)
Let's have a sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet time
あまいあまいあまいあまい時間を過ごしましょ
There's a whole lot of this spice (haa…)
胸いっぱいのこの香辛料も(はぁ...)
With all the love we put in, it might have been too much
入れ過ぎちゃうくらい愛を込めました
Let's eat it all, without leaving anything (hee haa!)
残さず全部めしあがれ (ひ~は~!)
Next is Happy Birthday!
次はハッピーバースデー
Happy MiniPati birthday
ハッピー ミニパティバースデー
Fluffy and sparkling
フワフワキラキラ
I’ll cast a magic spell on the cake!
魔法をかけちゃお!
Happy MiniPati birthday
ハッピー ミニパティバースデー
I wonder if it’ll turn out yummy?
美味しく出来るかな?
My heart’s hammering in my chest, hurry up and take a bite
胸がドキドキ 早く食べてね
Bon appetite with my sweet-art
スイーツアートを召し上がれ
Time to cook as if
お皿のキャンバスに
I were painting using the plate as a canvas
絵を描くみたいにクックタイム
Renoir, Monet, Picasso: cuisine is an art
ルノワール モネ ピカソ 料理はアートです
A pink cherry blossom chiffon cake
ピンク 桜のシフォンケーキ
White rice flour dumplings
ホワイト 白玉おだんご
Beige pudding ice cream
ベージュ プリンアイスクリーム
A red berry sauce mix
レッド MIX ベリーソース
My fork and spoon have the boldness of a paintbrush:
フォークとスプーンが絵筆の大胆さ,
composition, then colour
構図, そして彩り
Instead of using our left brain, Let's have lightbulbs go off in our right-brain PING!
左脳よりも右脳でひらめけ ピピピピッ
Shining! Cook! MiniPati!
キラキラ クック ミニパティ!
The finishing touch is a magical jelly
仕上げは魔法のゼリー
The cherry blossom petals flutter, please have a taste of this beautiful spring
桜の花びら ヒラリ 春うらら 召しませ
You wolf it down and the plate gleams white once again
ペロリたいらげて ピカピカのお皿に戻る
That smile of yours, That's definitely art right there
君のその笑顔 それこそがアートです
The sparkling breeze's art museum, And only one visitor
キラキラ風の美術館 観客はたった一人
But rather than worldwide recognition, hearing “It’s yummy” makes me happy
世界が認めるよりも 「おいしい」が嬉しい
Shining! Cook! MiniPati!
キラキラ クック ミニパティ!
The finishing touch is a magical jelly
仕上げは魔法のゼリー
The cherry blossom petals flutter, please have a taste of this beautiful spring
桜の花びら ヒラリ 春うらら 召しませ